



DERSAK HARIDAS DERSAK HARIDAS (Featured) Business Analyst with over 4+ years of experience in gathering and writing requirements, the architectural document, project management, software requirements analysis, user stories, acceptance criteria, data analytics, data analysis. Current Designation: Business Analyst Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 3 Month(s) Current Company: Markuplab Technologies (P) Ltd Notice Period: 1 Month Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical] Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Role: Business Analyst Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried Key Skills: Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Business Process Modeling, Software Development Methodologies, Agile, Data Analysis, Advanced Excel, Tableau, Risk Management, Statistical Analysis, Data Analytics Data Visualization Use Cases

Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Verified : Number | Email - id

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Business Analyst with over 4+ years of experience in gathering and writing requirements, the architectural document, project management, software requirements analysis, user stories, acceptance criteria, data analytics, data analysis, and Data Visualization, Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Risk Modelling, Data Modelling, Business Process flow diagram & Agile solutions. Good analytical, organizational skills, excellent interpersonal skills, and able to work within a team with abilities in achieving organizational goals. Able to effectively communicate with the senior management and coordinate with team members. Passionate about learning new things or tools every day.

Work Experience

Markuplab Technologies (P) Ltd as Business Analyst

Aug 2020 to Till Date

Technology Used: MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, MS Word, Draw.io, Visual Paradigm, Jira, Lucid chart, Xmind

- * Analyze the new project requirements
- * Prepare the mind maps, scope/architectural documents/wireframes based on the analysis and collect the approval from the respective
- * Discuss and explain the projects with the Production Manager and the development/QA team as needed.
- * Review the project progress and deliverables to ensure maximum client satisfaction.
- * Prepare and share the periodical status updates with the stakeholders of the projects.
- * Conduct/coordinate client meetings & calls as per the need.
- * Driving the project and setting different milestones
- * Making sure to review the targets that are achieved at every milestone.
- * Providing project reports and projections.

Allianz Technology as Operation Analyst

Apr 2018 to Nov 2019

Technology Used: Tableau/RMS. MS Excel

* Provide data analysis and data Analytics for Engineering Actuarial analysts team in the Allianz US Team for Contractors All Risks (CAR)

and Erection All Risks (EAR).

- * Co-ordinate with the Engineering Underwriters and collect risk related information.
- * Execution of various data quality checks including root cause analysis.
- * Sort compare and analyze data from multiple data joins.
- * Compile and join data from multiple sources to policy level reports and location level reports.
- * Model the risk and provide CAT Modelling reports to the Underwriters, Actuarial analysts, with a brief explanation on the results generated

which provides insight to the Underwriters to price the risk effectively and efficiently.

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Netroxe IT solutions Pvt Ltd as Business Analyst

Mar 2016 to Apr 2018

Technology Used: MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, MS Word, Xmind, GitHub

- ? Gather requirements from clients transiting and simplifying the requirements to the Senior Business Analyst Team.
- ? Closing Discussion with technical team, to find a proper solution to meet client?s expectation.
- ? Prepare exact and detailed Functional Specification Documents, Requirement Specification documents.
- ? Prepare system requirements to user stories, use case diagram, workflow diagram and Sequence diagram.
- ? Produce annual, quarterly, and monthly, daily data reports, reporting products, and analytic to Senior Business Analyst Team.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Anna University in 2014

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Cert Prep: Scrum Master

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

	Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
	WINDOWS 10		2020	4 Year(s) 2 Month(s)
ľ	GitHub, Xmind, Visual Paradigm		2016	4 Year(s) 2 Month(s)
ľ	RMS ,Tableau, Jira, Lucid chart, draw.io		2016	4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent
Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.